What's wrong?
Hey.
Haru-kun?
Hey!
Come on, please say something!
Haru-kun!
I'm sorry, Haru-kun.
I'm sorry.
I know I shouldn't cry, but...
It's hard to endure...
Because it's Haru-kun.
Sumomo-chan...
I'm sorry. I shouldn't keep on crying.
You know, Sumomo-chan...
Everyone has something that they like or treasure.
Yes.
And for everyone, there is something they must do everyday.
For me, it's work...
And for Sumomo-chan and Nako-chan, it's school.
Yes.
But you know...
Sometimes, there are times where you throw away everything,
and protect the thing that is important to you.
Sometimes...
When that happens even if you cry or scream...
it is nothing to be ashamed of.
That's right.
S-Sensei...
Nako-chan.
You don't need to push yourself, Sumomo.
Nako-chan!
Haru-kun... Haru-kun did it for me...
I... I...
And for that reason, Tsuwabuki-kun was hospitalized at the local hospital.
Tsuwabuki hospitalized?
Leave of absence, they say.
Isn't he going out with Akihime?
Seriously?
Well, even though I say hospitalization, he is just getting rest so there is no need to worry.
Well then...
Sumomo-chan.
Sumomo-chan went to visit, right?
Tsuwabuki, how was he?
He was fine a few days ago, wasn't he?
Just what kind of illness...
Truthfully, it wasn't something that even needed visiting.
Right, Sumomo?
Yeah.
But, but...
Sumomo-chan, you must be worrying a lot.
Right?
Why did he suddenly...?
I'm alright.
Haru-kun will come back soon.
I'm sure that... pretty soon...
I'm sure...
Even though it's my fault,
why...
Yuuki.
What?
Sumomo doesn't...
No, she doesn't blame Yuuki at the slightest.
Therefore...
Therefore, you don't need to be so hard on yourself.
This Recipe is...
Could it be...?
Impossible. It's too difficult.
Sumomo-chan can't...
But...
You've cleaned much better today than before.
Thank you, Matsuda.
No, what I did was something a butler should do.
Thank you for doing this for me, Matsuda.
It is an honor!
Miss, Matsuda is working very hard-
Miss!
What seems to be the problem?
To return this early...
If you'd have called, I would've gone straight away to pick you up.
But more importantly, are you feeling sick or something?
Should I bring some medicine?
Or maybe something war-
M-Miss.
What happened, Miss?
Miss!
Haru-kun will come back soon.
I'm sure that... pretty soon...
I'm sure...
It's my fault, isn't it?
It's natural that I should take the blame.
Why? Why aren't you even blaming me at all?
So, Sumomo-chan...
You said you were able to use the Recipe called "Timu Forna Mei," right?
Yes.
It was like things around me slowed down.
Well, there is a more advanced Recipe.
If you can use a Recipe called "Tim Forna Principatu,"
you might be able to turn back Yuki's time.
And if you return to the time before he revealed his identity,
Tsuwabuki-kun might be able to return.
Is that true?
But this...
This is a very difficult Recipe.
I'm not sure how well it will go.
Sumomo.
Sensei, I'll... I'll do it.
No matter how difficult it may be...
If I don't do it, Haru-kun will...
Haru-kun will...
Well then, for Figurare's power to be at its fullest...
Yes.
Let's do it when the moon is full.
Sumomo doesn't...
No, she doesn't blame Yuuki at the slightest.
Miss, I brought some hot tea.
Miss?
Miss!
Where are you going?
That light is...
Timu Forna Principatu
Are you okay?
You've been practicing this so much. You're tired, aren't you?
It's very difficult to control.
But I want to keep trying a little harder.
Sumomo...
Timu Forna Principatu.
Impossible.
There's no way that it'll work.
But...
No matter how much I try, it isn't going well.
And...
It's harder than any of the Recipes I've used so far.
Sumomo...
To be that tired...
It's not surprising... for such a difficult Recipe.
Miss.
What seems to be the problem?
To suddenly say that you wish to go to the kitchen...
And lately, you've been going out alone at night.
It's not to collect stardrops either, and...
Ah! If there is a need for a boxed lunch, I will gladly prepare it.
Then there's no point!
Yes?
Matsuda!
Y-Yes?
C-Cooking, how do you do it?
One more night...
Tonight, without a doubt...
I'll control time to make the withered flower blossom.
Timu Forna Principatu
I did it!
You did it!
Amazing, Sumomo.
You made it in time.
Yeah, thanks Nako-chan.
You've done well.
Sumomo?
I'm okay. It's just that I'm out of strength.
Sumomo, to do it up to this point...
Thanks.
It's because Nako-chan kept encouraging me.
No, Sumomo gave it her best, that's why.
I'm sure that everything will go just fine tomorrow.
Yeah.
Hot!
Miss!
A-A-Are you okay?
Matsuda will take care of this...
I'm fine, let's continue.
But Miss...
At last, tonight...
If I... If I fail...
It's possible, if it is Sumomo.
Yuki-chan.
You can definitely do it, Sumomo.
Haru-kun.
I'm scared, Haru-kun.
Sumomo!
Sumomo.
Akihime.
No!
Yuki-chan.
Mother?
Mother...
Oh my, I fell asleep.
Huh?
This is...
Eat this and do well.
There's no point if you collapse before you save Tsuwabuki, is there?
Yuuki Nona.
Nona-chan.
I couldn't eat these past few days.
Thank you, Nona-chan.
It's delicious.
This is a magic circle which amplifies the power of your spell.
Now, Sumomo-chan,
put Yuki-chan down in the middle.
Yes.
Yuki-chan.
Haru-kun.
Please wait for me.
It'd be great if the ability of the Ladle could be amplified from this.
Now, swinging the Ladle in front of Yuki-chan,
and reciting the Recipe is all that's left.
Good luck.
Yes.
Nako-chan, sorry to make you worry all the time.
I'm sure it will go well.
Sumomo.
Yeah, good luck to you.
Sensei, Nako-chan.
And Nona-chan.
Thank you.
Sumomo.
Sumomo-chan.
Timu Forna Principatu!
Sumomo!
Sumomo-chan!
Pull yourself together, Prima Plam!
You can't lose!
You're going to meet him, Tsuwabuki, aren't you?!
Aspalas-san... No. Nona-chan.
Yes!
Do your best.
It's okay. It'll definitely work.
If it is you two...
Have faith.
That was...
Now!
Right!
Yuki-chan, thank you.
Haru-kun, come back.
Yuuki.
It's fine. It definitely was a success.
Haru-kun.
Sumomo.
Haru-kun!
Umm, Sumomo?
Is this... the school's grounds?
Eh. Sumomo? Sumomo?
We'll tell you all about it later, Tsuwabuki.
Yaeno, Yuuki too.
I'm sorry to call you all the way here.
It wasn't because of me.
It was because of the strength of those two girls.
Those two are really amazing.
Sensei, thank you very much.
No, it's the result of Sumomo-chan's effort.
The power of love really is invincible.
Sumomo!
Yuuki said she'll give us rides!
I'll go thank Nona-chan.
Well then...
Tsuwabuki-kun.
Yes?
I'll ask just in case, but...
Right now...
What month is it?
Umm, what month you say?
It's May.
Right now, it's November... Tsuwabuki-kun.
What if a precious memory disappeared?
What do you mean?
What if two lovers lost their memory of their time together?
That is...
If I lost my precious memory of being with Nobuko-san...!
Obviously...
That's not it! Idiot!